Chris J. Harris

3900 Jupiter Lane Apt B107 Butte, MT 59701 (406) 490-6377

cjharris9908@gmail.com

Professional Profile

I served in the United States Army as a Cavalry Scout from February 2011 until December 2014. I changed my MOS to an Information Technology Specialist in January 2015 and worked in this field until my contract ended in October 2018. My reason behind this change was to help me pursue a career in the Information Technology field. Currently, I am working as an armed security guard for MaxSent in Butte, MT.

Key Skills and Qualifications

- Information Technology
- Information Security
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Supervisory Experience
- Help Desk/Troubleshooting

- Armed Security
- Critical Thinking Skills
- Security Clearance
- Verbal and Written Communication
- Military Experience

Education

Butte High School

Graduated May 2005

• Graduated and earned high school diploma in May 2005.

Work History

Armed Security Officer

MaxSent, Butte, MT

October 2018 – Present

• Controls access to federal facilities through the admittance process; precludes unauthorized access to facilities; and am trained to prevent the conversion, theft, or intentional destruction of physical assets.

Information Technology Specialist

January 2015 – October 2018

United States Army, Fort Stewart, GA

- Systems administrator for over 100 sustainment information systems.
- My department completed over 3,000 troubleshooting ticket resolutions.

Cavalry Scout

February 2011 – December 2014

United States Army, Schofield Barracks, HI

- Assigned to be the direct supervisor of junior soldiers.
- Proficient in the use of GPS, including map reading and land navigation.
- Trained in security drills and escalation of force.

Tire and Lube Technician

June 2006 – February 2011

Whalen Tire, Butte, MT

- Performed maintenance on customers' vehicles, including: installing new tires, performing oil changes, replacing tie rods and ball joints, and conducting alignments.
- On-call one weekend a month and one night a week.
- Helped people in need of tire repair or other related services in an efficient, professional manner.

Cashier/Clerk

September 2002 – May 2006

East Gate IGA, Butte, MT

• Responsibilities included: cashiering, assisting customers, and bringing customers' groceries to their vehicles.